[{"quizName": "Basic Addition", "grade": "school", "quizID": "1", "subGrade": "1st", "topic": "Arithmetics", "quizDisc": "Basic Arithmetics problems for 1st grade Students. This quiz is on Addition", "quizHour": "1", "quizMinutes": "30", "quizOwner": "drive.c.adarsh@gmail.com", "quizTarget": ["all"], "questions": [{"question": "1+1?", "options": ["10", "1", "2", "3", "4"], "correctAnswer": ["2"], "score": "1", "selected": []}, {"question": "1+2?", "options": ["10", "1", "2", "3", "4"], "correctAnswer": ["3"], "score": "1", "selected": []}, {"question": "1+10?", "options": ["10", "1", "2", "3", "4", "11"], "correctAnswer": ["1", "11"], "score": "2", "selected": []}, {"question": "1+0?", "options": ["0", "1"], "correctAnswer": ["1"], "score": "1", "selected": []}]}, {"quizName": "Basic Subtraction", "grade": "school", "quizID": "2", "subGrade": "1st", "topic": "Arithmetics", "quizDisc": "Basic Arithmetics problems for 1st grade Students. This quiz is on Subtraction", "quizHour": "1", "quizMinutes": "30", "quizOwner": "chekodu.adarsh@gmail.com", "quizTarget": ["all"], "questions": [{"question": "1-1?", "options": ["0", "1", "2", "3", "4"], "correctAnswer": ["0"], "score": "1", "selected": []}, {"question": "2-1?", "options": ["0", "1", "2", "3", "4"], "correctAnswer": ["1", "0"], "score": "1", "selected": []}, {"question": "10-8?", "options": ["10", "1", "2", "3", "4", "11"], "correctAnswer": ["2"], "score": "2", "selected": []}, {"question": "1-0?", "options": ["0", "1"], "correctAnswer": ["1"], "score": "1", "selected": []}]}, {"quizName": "Basic English", "quizID": "3", "grade": "school", "subGrade": "1st", "topic": "Arithmetics", "quizDisc": "Basic English problems for 3rd grade Students. This quiz is on fill in thee blanks", "quizHour": "1", "quizMinutes": "30", "quizOwner": "chekodu.adarsh@gmail.com", "quizTarget": ["all"], "questions": [{"question": "Appl_?", "options": ["e", "a", "o", "i", "k"], "correctAnswer": ["e"], "score": "1", "selected": []}, {"question": "Tre_?", "options": ["e", "a", "o", "i", "y"], "correctAnswer": ["3"], "score": "1", "selected": []}, {"question": "M_ngo?", "options": ["a", "b", "e", "y", "k", "g"], "correctAnswer": ["1", "11"], "score": "2", "selected": []}]}, {"quizName": "Basic Division", "quizID": "4", "grade": "school", "subGrade": "1st", "topic": "Arithmetics", "quizDisc": "Basic Arithmetics problems for 4th grade Students. This quiz is on Division", "quizHour": "1", "quizMinutes": "30", "quizOwner": "chekodu.adarsh@gmail.com", "quizTarget": ["all"], "questions": [{"question": "2 / 1?", "options": ["10", "2", "0.5", "3", "4"], "correctAnswer": ["2"], "score": "1", "selected": []}, {"question": "1/2?", "options": ["10", "0.5", "2", "3", "4"], "correctAnswer": ["3"], "score": "1", "selected": []}]}, {"quizName": "Maths Basics", "grade": "School", "quizID": "5", "subGrade": "2nd", "topic": "maths", "quizDisc": "Basic Maths Question fro 2nd grade students", "quizHour": "0", "quizMinutes": "10", "quizOwner": "chekodu.adarsh@gmail.com", "quizTarget": ["all"], "questions": [{"question": "1+1=?", "score": "1", "selected": [], "options": ["1", "2", "3", "4"], "correctAnswer": ["2"]}, {"question": "10x10=?", "score": "3", "selected": [], "options": ["10", "100", "1", "1000"], "correctAnswer": ["100"]}, {"question": "2+2=?", "score": "1", "selected": [], "options": ["2", "4", "6"], "correctAnswer": []}]}, {"quizName": "NTSE Prep-2", "grade": "Entrance Exam", "quizID": "6", "subGrade": "NTSE", "topic": "Algebra", "quizDisc": "", "quizHour": "0", "quizMinutes": "20", "quizSubject": "", "quizMedium": "English", "quizOwner": "chekodu.adarsh@gmail.com", "quizTarget": ["all"], "questions": [{"question": "2+2", "score": "1", "selected": [], "options": ["2", "4", "8"], "correctAnswer": ["4"]}, {"question": "4+4", "score": "1", "selected": [], "options": ["4", "8", "6"], "correctAnswer": ["4"]}, {"question": "10+10", "score": "1", "selected": [], "options": ["10", "100", "1", "20"], "correctAnswer": ["10"]}]}]